Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Anthony J. Viola Papers, 1968-2009 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Anthony J. Viola papers 1968-2009 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company.
58 linear feet Extent: 6000 Items
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT), founded in 1864, is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Anthony Viola worked as a Creative executive with a number of agencies before retiring as Senior Art Director with JWT. The Anthony J. Viola Papers span the years 1968-2009 and document Viola's career, especially his role as an art director at JWT's New York, Chicago, and Lisbon offices. The papers include some correspondence and other office files but the bulk of the collection consists of artwork for print advertisements and television storyboards; along with videocassettes, videotapes, DVDs and 16mm films of television commercials created by Viola. The papers cover JWT offices in Chicago; New York; Milan (Italy); Buenos Aires (Argentina); Lisbon (Portugal); and Santiago (Chile). Key clients include Bell Atlantic; the City of Boston; Citibank; Dole; Kodak; Interstate Bakeries; Johnson & Johnson; Kellogg; Kimberly Clark; Kraft Foods; Mars; Miller beer; Nestlé; Pepsi; Pfizer; Reckitt & Benckiser; Rolex; Sears; Schlitz; Unilever; and Warner Lambert. Most of the files are in English; some materials are in Spanish. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.00757
Language: Material in English Spanish
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, original audiovisual materials are closed to researchers until use copies can be made.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Anthony J. Viola Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2009.
Biographical Note
Chronology List
1960 Associate Degree, Applied Arts and Sciences, State University of New York, Long Island
1964 BA, State University of New York, Long Island
1960-1969 Art Director, General Electric Company in New York
1968 Graduated from General Electric School of Advertising, program in Advertising and Sales Promotion
1969-1974 Art Supervisor, Kenyon & Eckert Advertising in Boston
1974-1976 Head Art Director, Hill Holliday Conners-Cosmopulos, Inc. in Boston
1976-1978 Vice President, Associate Creative Director, McCann-Erickson Inc., Chicago
1978-1981 Vice President, Associate Creative Director, JWT Chicago
1981-1986 Vice President, Associate Art Director, JWT New York
1986-1988 Vice President, Associate Creative Director, Backer Spielvogel Bates, New York, N.Y.
1989-1990 Vice President, Senior Creative Group Head, Ketchum Advertising, New York, N.Y.
1990-2009 Senior Art Director at J.Walter Thompson in New York, Chicago and Lisbon
2000-2005 Visiting Professor, University of Syracuse, Newhouse School of Communication and VPA Summer Masters Class
Collection Overview
The Anthony J. Viola Papers span the years 1968-2009 and document Viola's career, especially his role as an art director at JWT's New York, Chicago, and Lisbon offices. The papers include some correspondence and other office files but the bulk of the collection consists of artwork for print advertisements and television storyboards; along with videocassettes, videotapes, DVDs and 16mm films of television commercials created by Viola. The papers cover JWT offices in Chicago; New York; Milan (Italy); Buenos Aires (Argentina); Lisbon (Portugal); and Santiago (Chile). Key clients include Bell Atlantic; the City of Boston; Citibank; Dole; Kodak; Interstate Bakeries; Johnson & Johnson; Kellogg; Kimberly Clark; Kraft Foods; Mars; Miller beer; Nestlé; Pepsi; Pfizer; Reckitt & Benckiser; Rolex; Sears; Schlitz; Unilever; and Warner Lambert. Most of the files are in English; some materials are in Spanish.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is organized into three Series: General Records; Advertising Designs; and Audiovisual Materials.
The General Records series is organized into three categories: Office Files; Personal Files; and Use Copies of Audiovisual Materials. Office Files includes correspondence and memoranda for General Electric, and the JWT Milan (Italy) and Santiago (Chile) Offices. Personal Files contains private correspondence, resumes and biographical sketches. Use Copies of Audiovisual Materials contains use copies of Viola's television commercials and scans of sketches, print advertisements, TV boards and storyboards from the 1970s to 2000s. The Advertising Designs series contains the bulk of the collections' content. This series is divided into categories according to form and format: small- and large-format Artwork; small- and large-format Laminated Print Advertisements; Mounted Advertising Designs; and Oversized Materials. Arranged alphabetically by brand. Artwork contains mostly sketches, drafts and proofs of television commercial storyboards and print advertisements, as well as some attached notes. The Laminated Print Advertisements contains proofs of print advertisements, laminated for use in presentations. Mounted Advertising Designs consist of print advertisements and storyboards that have been mounted on mat board or foamcore board. Oversized Materials contains sketches, drafts and final proofs of television commercial storyboards, sketches and final proofs of print advertisements, as well as some screen prints and posters. The Audiovisual Series contains television commercials, presentation and sample reels in 16mm film, 1-inch videotape, VHS videocassette, Betacam, and DVD formats. Use copies are available for some of these commercials. Arranged alphabetically by brand or title.
Subject Headings
Viola, Anthony J.; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. Buenos Aires Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Lisbon Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Milan Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Santiago (Chile) Office; Bell Atlantic Corporation; Citibank (New York, N.Y.); Dole Food Company; Eastman Kodak Company; Interstate Bakeries Corporation; Johnson & Johnson; Kellogg Company; Kimberly-Clark Corporation; Kraft Foods Company; Mars, Incorporated; Miller Brewing Company; Nestlé; PepsiCo, Inc.; Chas. Pfizer & Co; Reckitt Benckiser (Firm); Montres Rolex S.A.; Sears, Roebuck and Company; Jos. Schlitz Brewing Co.; Unilever (Firm); Warner-Lambert Company; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- Argentina; Advertising agencies -- Chile; Advertising agencies -- Europe; Advertising agencies -- Italy; Advertising agencies -- Portugal; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising executives; Advertising executives -- Chile; Advertising executives -- Europe; Advertising executives -- Italy; Advertising executives -- Portugal; Advertising executives -- United States; Television advertising; Television advertising -- Argentina; Television advertising -- Chile; Television advertising -- Europe; Television advertising -- Italy; Television advertising -- Portugal; Television advertising -- United States; 16mm; DVDs; Proofs; Videocassettes; Videotapes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
John F. Dingham Papers
Wallace W. Elton Papers
In addition, other advertising Art Directors' papers held by the Hartman Center include:
Gene Federico Papers
Charles McKinney Papers
Garrett Orr Papers
Klaus Reikowski Papers
Ben Rosen Papers
Robert S. Smith Papers
Contents of Collection
- General Files, 1968-2009, (1 box)
  Includes corporate and private correspondence, memoranda, resumes and DVDs of television commercials along with scans of print advertisements. Firms represented include General Electric, and the JWT Milan (Italy) and Santiago (Chile) Offices. Organized into two categories: Office Files and Personal Files Arranged alphabetically.
  - Office Files, 1968-1982
    - General Electric Company, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company (Box 1)
      - General correspondence, 1980-1985, (6 folders) (Box 1)
      - JWT Chile Office, 1980-1984 (Box 1)
      - JWT Milan Office, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
      - Milan Office Creative Book, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Personal Files, 1981 and undated (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Resume and Biography, undated (Box 1)
- Advertising Designs, 1971-2009 and undated, (19 boxes) (Box 1)
  Includes sketches, drawings, mock-ups, and storyboards. A portion are laminated; others are mounted on mat board or foamcore. Arranged by form and format size, therein alphabetically by product name.
  - Artwork--small-format, 1976-2009 and undated (Box 1)
    - Abilify, 2005-2006 (Box 2)
    - Acterma, 2008 (Box 2)
    - Acutrim, undated (Box 2)
    - Associated Mills, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Band-Aid and Neosporin, 2008-2009 (Box 2)
    - Band-Aid Ultra Strips, 2007-2008, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Bengay, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Blem (Argentina), 1980 (Box 2)
    - Cottonelle, undated, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Country Recipe Pasta Salad, undated (Box 2)
    - Crispix Mix, undated (Box 2)
    - Dole Fruit, 1987 (Box 2)
    - ECU Vegetables, undated (Box 2)
    - EPT Pregnancy Test, undated (Box 2)
    - Glade (Argentina), 1980 (Box 2)
    - Glass Plus, 2006, (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Glo-Clot (Argentina), 1980 (Box 2)
    - HBO, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
    - Jake's Diet Cola, undated (Box 2)
    - Kleenex, undated (Box 2)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
    - Klear (Argentina), 1980 (Box 2)
    - Kodak, 1986 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Kodak (Brazil), 1985 (Box 2)
    - Kodak (Chile), 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    - Lever 2000, undated (Box 2)
    - Lime Away, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Listerine, 2000-2009 and undated, (6 folders) (Box 3)
    - Listerine Advanced, 2004 (Box 3)
    - Listerine Daytime/Nighttime, 2008 (Box 3)
    - Listerine Daytime, 2008, (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Listerine Nighttime, 2008, (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Listerine Pocket Packs, 2003 (Box 3)
    - Listerine Print Advertisements, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Listerine Smart Rinse, 2007 (Box 3)
    - Listerine Total Care, 2008 (Box 3)
    - Listerine Vibrant White, 2008 (Box 3)
    - Listerine Whitening, 2004 (Box 3)
    - Listerine Whitening Strips, 2008 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Listerine and Reach, 2008 (Box 3)
    - Lubriderm, 2000-2002 (Box 3)
    - Lysol Disinfectant, 2004 (Box 3)
    - Lysol Food Service Sanitizer, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Lysol Toilet Bowl Cleaner, 2004 (Box 3)
    - Merita Bread, undated (Box 3)
    - Merrill Lynch, 2004, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Miller Lite, undated (Box 4)
    - Neosporin, 2005-2006, (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Nescafé (Chile), 1981 (Box 4)
    - Nestea, undated (Box 4)
    - Nestea Sugar Free, 1983 (Box 4)
    - Neutra Air, 2006 (Box 4)
    - Nutra-Sweet, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Off Repellent (Argentina), 1980 (Box 4)
    - Oscar Mayer, undated (Box 4)
    - Pepcid E-Z Chews, 2007 (Box 4)
    - Pepsi, 1979 (Box 4)
    - Pepsi (Argentina), 1986 (Box 4)
    - Pepsi International, undated (Box 4)
    - Pepsi: Coola, San Citro, Jazz, Squeeze, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Pepsi: Jake's Cola, Jazz, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Philadelphia Cream Cheese, 2008, (5 folders) (Box 4)
    - Preferred Stock, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Pristiq, 2007-2008, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Purell, 2004-2008, (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - Quaker Meat Spreads (Argentina), 1980 (Box 5)
    - Quaker Pasta (Argentina), 1980 (Box 5)
    - Quaker Polenta (Argentina), 1980 (Box 5)
    - Quaker Sardines (Argentina), 1980 (Box 5)
    - Raid (Argentina), 1980, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Rolaids, 2004, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Rotateq, undated (Box 5)
    - Sears, Roebuck and Company, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Scott Towels, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Skippy Peanut Butter, 1977 (Box 5)
    - Slice, 1984, (4 folders) (Box 5)
    - Stouffer's, undated (Box 5)
    - Sunkist Pre-Teen Multivitamin, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Trident Advantage, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Uncle Ben's Rice, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Veet, 2006 (Box 5)
    - Visine, 2007, (4 folders) (Box 5)
    - Wisk, undated (Box 5)
    - Zyrtec, 2004, (4 folders) (Box 5)
  - Artwork--large format, 1980-2009 and undated (Box 5)
    - Abilify, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Acterma, 2008 (Box 6)
    - Band-Aid Global, 2008 (Box 6)
    - Band-Aid and Neosporin, 2008-2009 (Box 6)
    - Band-Aid Ultra Strips, 2008 (Box 6)
    - Boston Bicentennial, undated (Box 6)
    - Cottonelle, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Glass Plus, 2006 (Box 6)
    - Fidelity Investments, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
    - Listerine, 2004-2006 (Box 7)
    - Listerine Advanced, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Listerine Nighttime and Daytime, 2008 (Box 7)
    - Listerine Pocket Packs, 2005 (Box 7)
    - Listerine Smart Rinse, 2006-2007 (Box 7)
    - Listerine Total Care, 2008 (Box 7)
    - Listerine Whitening, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Lubriderm, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Lysol Dissenfectant, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Lysol Toilet Bowl Cleaner, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Menopause Relief--Newsflash.com, undated (Box 7)
    - Merrill Lynch, 2003 (Box 7)
    - Neosporin, 2004-2007 (Box 7)
    - Neutra Air, 2006 (Box 7)
    - Pam Shriver Nutrition Tips, undated (Box 7)
    - Pepcid, 2006-2007 (Box 7)
    - Pepsi, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Philadelphia Cream Cheese, 2008-2009 (Box 8)
    - Pristiq, 2008 (Box 8)
    - Purell, 2005 (Box 8)
    - Rolaids, 2005 (Box 8)
    - Scott Tissues, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Slice, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Sudafed P.E. Strips, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Sylvia Porter's Financial Tips, undated (Box 8)
    - Veet, 2006 (Box 8)
    - Visine, 2006 (Box 8)
    - Zyrtec, 2006-2007, (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Laminated print advertisements--small format, 1971-2003 and undated (Box 8)
    - Canadian Breeding Laboratories, circa 1971-1973 (Box 9)
    - Citibank, 1995-1997, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Charles River (Lakeview) Breeding Laboratories, circa 1971-1973 (Box 9)
    - Dole Fruit, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Grinnell Valves, circa 1971-1973 (Box 9)
    - Hood, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Hood Cottage Cheese, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Jake's Cola, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Kennedy Valve, undated (Box 9)
    - Kodak, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
    - Lender's Bagels, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Lubriderm, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Mimosa Butter, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Mimosa Yogurt, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Rolex, 1999-2002 (Box 9)
    - The Wall Street Journal, undated (Box 9)
    - Warner Lambert International, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Laminated print advertisements--large format, 1971-2000 and undated (Box 9)
    - Bell Atlantic, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Citibank, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Colonial Meats, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Findus, undated (Box 10)
    - Hood Cottage Cheese, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Kodak (George Cukor, Director), 1981 (Box 10)
    - The Last Hurrah!, menus, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
    - The Mayor's Older Bostonians, undated (Box 10)
    - Philip Morris Companies Inc., 1986 (Box 10)
    - Philips, undated (Box 10)
    - Rolex, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Sears, The Men's Store, undated (Box 10)
    - The South Shore Conservatory of Music, undated (Box 10)
    - The Wall Street Journal, undated (Box 10)
    - Warner-Lambert International, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Mounted advertising designs, 1988-1996 and undated (Box 10)
    - Listerine Cool Mint, undated (Box 11)
    - Listerine Smart Rinse, undated (Box 11)
    - Listerine Whitening, undated (Box 11)
    - Pepcid E-Z Chews, undated (Box 11)
    - Pristiq, undated (Box 11)
    - Purell, undated (Box 11)
    - University Club of New York Promotion, undated (Box 11)
    - Visine, undated (Box 11)
    - Zyrtec, undated (Box 11)
    - Miller Lite, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Uncle Ben's Rice, undated (Box 12)
    - Cottonelle, undated (Box 13)
    - Country Recipe Pasta Salad, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Fidelity Investments, undated (Box 13)
    - Fidelity Investments, undated (Box 14)
    - Uncle Ben's Rice, undated (Box 14)
    - Cincinatti Rascals (rugby team), undated (Box 15)
    - Lever 2000, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Lever 2000, 1996 (continued) (Box 16)
    - Lever 2000, 1996 (continued) (Box 17)
    - Lubriderm, undated (Box 17)
    - Lubriderm, undated (continued) (Box 18)
    - Miller Lite, undated (Box 18)
    - Scott Tissues, undated (Box 18)
    - Scott Tissues, undated (continued) (Box 19)
    - Snickers, undated (Box 19)
    - Trident Advantage, undated (Box 19)
  - Oversized Materials, 1972-2007 and undated (Box 19)
    - Bath and Closet, undated (Box 20)
    - Cable Shop TV, 1981 (Box 20)
    - Fidelity Investments, undated (Box 20)
    - JWT T-Shirt Design for The Corporate Challenge run, 1997 (Box 20)
    - Kodak, undated (Box 20)
    - Lever 2000, undated (Box 20)
    - Listerine, 2007 (Box 20)
    - New England Conservatory, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Pepsi International, undated (Box 20)
    - Screen Prints, 1988 (Box 20)
    - University Club of New York promotion, undated (Box 20)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2009 and undated, (17 boxes) (Box 20)
  - Originals, 1970-2008 and undated (Box 20)
    Restrictions on Access: Original audiovisual materials are closed to patrons until use copies can be made. Use copies exist for some items.
    - Umatic and VHS (Box 20)
      - 1. Acutrim. 1990 Jan. 18. Umatic. TRT: :15 (Box 21)
      - 2. Acutrim. 1990 Jan. 18. Umatic. TRT: :15 (Box 21)
      - 3. Acutrim. 1990 Apr. 4. VHS. TRT: 2:00 (Box 21)
      - 4. Boston. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 21)
      - 5. Cottonelle Wider Ripples. Undated. Umatic. TRT: :45 (Box 21)
      - 6. Cottonelle Wider Ripples. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 21)
      - 7. Cottonelle Fresh Rollwipes. 2001 Dec. 19. Umatic. TRT: :60 (Box 21)
      - 8. Dole. 1987 May 08. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 21)
      - 9. Dole. 1987 May 08. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 22)
      - 10. Dole Banana. 1987 Nov. 04. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 22)
      - 11. Dole Sales Presentation. undated. VHS. TRT: unknown (Box 22)
      - 12. Dow Jones Information Overload. 1998 Jun. 29. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 22)
      - 13. Kellogg's Bran Flakes. 1991 Feb. 07. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 22)
      - 14. Kellogg's Bran Flakes. 1991 May 09. Umatic. TRT: :60 (Box 22)
      - 15. Kellogg's Bran Flakes. 1991 May 28. Umatic. TRT: :60 (Box 22)
      - 16. Kellogg's Bran Flakes. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 22)
      - 17. Kellogg's Breakfast Mates. 2000. Umatic. TRT: :10 (Box 23)
      - 18. Kodak Baseball, 1984 Sept. 11. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 23)
      - 19. Kodak Sports, 1985 Aug. 30. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 23)
      - 20. Kodak. 1986 Nov. 10. Umatic. 2:00 (Box 23)
      - 21. Kodak Brazil--World Cup. Undated. Umatic. TRT: :45 (Box 23)
      - 22. Kodak 3 Pak. Undated. Umatic. TRT: :40 (Box 23)
      - 23. Kodak 4 Commercials. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 23)
      - 24. Kraft Real Mayonnaise. 1980 Jan. 14. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 23)
      - 25. Lipton Iced Tea Kickboxer, 2003 May 22. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 26. Listerine Tightrope, 1999 May 24. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 27. Listerine Mouthwash Humanity, 2003 Apr. 22. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 28. Lubriderm. 2000 Mar. 31. VHS. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 29. Lubriderm Daily UV. 2000 Apr. 21. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 30. Lubrderm Skin Firming Lotion. undated. VHS. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
      - 31. Mathew Brady Films Rain, 1992 Dec. 21. Umatic. TRT: :40 (Box 24)
      - 32. Mathew Brady Films. Rain, 1992. Umatic. (Box 24)
      - 33. Merita Lite Bread. 1989 Nov. 1. VHS. TRT: :40 (Box 24)
      - 34. Mimosa Yogurt You, 1993 Oct. 15. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 25)
      - 35. Mimosa Yogurt You. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 25)
      - 36. Miller Lite. 1988 Aug. 29. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 25)
      - 37. Nescafe. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 25)
      - 38. Nestea. 1983 May 23. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 39. 1983 Nestea Advertising. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box 25)
      - 40. Nestea 100%. 1984 Mar 28. Umatic. TRT: :60 (Box 25)
      - 41. Nestea Free. 1984 May 08. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 42. Oscar Mayer Cold Cuts. 1981 Apr. 20. Umatic. TRT: :90 (Box 26)
      - 43. Pepsi Brands. 1986 Feb. 13. VHS. TRT: 3:30 (Box 26)
      - 44. Pepsi Brands. 1986 Feb. 13. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 26)
      - 45. Pepsi International. 1986 Jan. 17. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 26)
      - 46. Pepsi International. 1986 Jan. 21. Umatic. TRT: :30 (Box 26)
      - 47. Pepsi International Sample Reel. 1986 Nov. 11. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box 26)
      - 48. Pepsi Jakes. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 26)
      - 49. Pepsi Jakes. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 26)
      - 50. Pepsi Jakes Sales Film. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 27)
      - 51. Pepsi Mexico. 1986 Jan. 17. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 27)
      - 52. Pep Rally--New York Office. 1982 Jun. 23. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 27)
      - 53. Reunion & Ringside. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 27)
      - 54. Schlitz Worth it. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 27)
      - 55. Schlitz. 1979 Apr. 17. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 27)
      - 56. Scott Tissues. 2000 May 10. Umatic. TRT: :45 (Box 27)
      - 57. Sumol--Lisbon Office. 1993 Oct. 15. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 27)
      - 56. Sumol. Undated. VHS. TRT: unknown (Box 27)
      - 57. Sunkist Vitamins Director's Cut. 1989 May 17. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 28)
      - 58. Sunkist Children's Multi Vitamins. 1989 Apr. 20. VHS. TRT: :30 (Box 28)
      - 59. Whirlpool Bath Spa--Associated Mills. Inc./Pollenex. 1977 Nov. 04. Umatic. TRT: :60 (Box 28)
      - 60. Presentation Reel--Hong Kong TV Print Sketches. 1989 Jan. 30. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 28)
        [Includes spots for Nestea; Dole; Kodak; Oscar Mayer; and Jake's Cola]
      - 61. Presentation Reel--Hong Kong Roll A. 1989 Jan. 20. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 28)
      - 62. Presentation Reel--Hong Kong Roll B. 1989 Jan. 20. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 28)
      - 64. Presentation Reel--Hong Kong Presentation. 1989 Jan. 18. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 28)
      - 63. Presentation Reel--Syracuse University. 1999 Nov. 04. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 28)
        [Includes spots for Merita; Hendries; Nestea; Kelloggs; Listerine; Sunkist; Kodak; Mimosa; Sumol; and Dow Jones]
      - 64. Presentation Reel--Syracuse University. 2000 Sept. 15. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 28)
        [Includes spots for Merita; Nestea; Kelloggs; Listerine; Sunkist; Kodak; Scott Tissues; Trident; Lubriderm; Mimosa; and Sumol]
      - 65. Presentation Reel--Syracuse University. 2002 Mar. 29. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 29)
      - 66. Presentation Reel--Syracuse University. 1999 Nov. 04. VHS. TRT: unknown (Box 29)
      - 67. Sample Reel--JWT Chicago. 1981 Apr. 20. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 29)
        [Includes spots for Schlitz; Jovan; Kodak; and Kraft]
      - 68. Sample Reel--JWT Chicago. 1981 Apr. 20. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 29)
        [Includes spots for City of Boston; New England Merchants Bank; Polaroid; Underwood Deviled Ham; B&M Baked Beans; Mass Bay United Fund; Sears Jeans; Boston Bicentennial; and Boston Red Sox]
      - 69. Sample Reel. 1986 Nov. 11. Umatic. TRT: 5:00. (Box 29)
        [Includes spots for Nestea; Kodak; and Oscar Mayer]
      - 70. Sample Reel. 1989 Jan. 26. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 29)
        [Includes spots for Nestea; Dole; Kodak; and Oscar Mayer]
      - 71. Sample Reel. 1989 Jan. 30. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 29)
      - 72. Sample Reel. 1989 Jan. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 29)